She's terminally ill
إنها مريضة بمرض عضال
and doesn't have much longer to live.
وليس لديها وقت أطول للعيش.
Who
من
is she?
هل هي؟
Xu Xixi, the daughter of Yongyu Capital.
Xu Xixi ، ابنة Yongyu Capital.
From now on,
من الان فصاعدا،
you have to imitate her behaviour, her expressions, her habits,
عليك أن تقلد سلوكها وتعبيراتها وعاداتها ،
until you can replace her
حتى يمكنك استبدالها
as Ms. Xu.
مثل السيدة شو.
I don't know what you're up to,
لا أعرف ما الذي تنوي فعله ،
but I won't do as you say.
لكنني لن أفعل كما تقول.
This is for your own good.
هذا هو لمصلحتك.
For my own good?
لبلدي الخير الخاصة؟
Which mother
أي أم
would do this to her child?
ستفعل هذا لطفلها؟
When I was a child, I even wondered
حتى أنني كنت أتساءل عندما كنت طفلاً
whether I was your child or not.
سواء كنت ابنك أم لا.
Of course you are my child.
بالطبع أنت طفلي.
Still, you have to be Xu Xixi.
لا يزال ، يجب أن تكون Xu Xixi.
You have no choice.
ليس لديك خيار.
Otherwise, both of us will die.
وإلا سيموت كلانا.
Ms. Xu, take care.
السيدة شو ، اعتني بنفسك.
All right.
حسنًا.
Go ahead.
تفضل.
But they just left.
لكنهم غادروا للتو.
If you can't even fool them,
إذا كنت لا تستطيع حتى خداعهم ،
how can you fool Xu Yongyu?
كيف تخدع Xu Yongyu؟
Come on. Just go.
تعال.  فقط اذهب.
Ms. Xu.
السيدة شو.
Call out all the people who were involved in the project.
قم باستدعاء جميع الأشخاص الذين شاركوا في المشروع.
Okay.
تمام.
Ms. Xu.
السيدة شو.
Are you sure you want to do the same project again?
هل أنت متأكد أنك تريد أن تفعل نفس المشروع مرة أخرى؟
Your cuticle is thin,
بشرتك رقيقة ،
if you cleanse it repeatedly...
إذا قمت بتنظيفه بشكل متكرر ...
Can you hear?
هل يمكنك السماع؟
Since you're not deaf,
بما أنك لست أصم ،
do I have to repeat myself?
هل علي أن أكرر نفسي؟
Sorry.
آسف.
We will have it ready.
سنجهزها.
This way, please.
من هذا الاتجاه من فضلك.
=Love of Replica=
= حب النسخة المتماثلة =
=Episode 8=
= الحلقة 8 =
(Unknown number)
(رقم مجهول)
(Why is my dad's phone)
(لماذا هاتف والدي)
(ringing at this time?)
(رنين في هذا الوقت؟)
(Who is it?)
(من هذا؟)
(Jiang Tiancheng)
(جيانغ تيانشينج)
Tiancheng?
تيانشينج؟
Can you check
هل لك ان تتحقق
the location of this phone number for me?
موقع رقم الهاتف هذا بالنسبة لي؟
Wait,
انتظر،
he called on my dad's cell phone.
اتصل على هاتف والدي الخلوي.
(The only person in the world who loves me is gone)
(رحل الشخص الوحيد في العالم الذي يحبني)
(and the person I love has never been honest with me.)
(والشخص الذي أحبه لم يكن صادقًا معي أبدًا).
(Since no one cares about An Yue's existence,)
(بما أنه لا أحد يهتم بوجود An Yue ،)
(as you wish,)
(كما تتمنا،)
(there will be only Xu Xixi from now on.)
(لن يكون هناك سوى Xu Xixi من الآن فصاعدًا.)
Old man.
رجل عجوز.
I regained my memory.
استعدت ذاكرتي.
Really?
حقًا؟
So,
لذا،
do you recall the illness too?
هل تتذكر المرض ايضا؟
Yes.
نعم.
I don't have many days left to live, do I?
لم يبق لي أيام كثيرة لأعيشها ، أليس كذلك؟
Don't talk nonsense.
لا تتحدث عن هراء.
Xixi.
يتبول.
Don't do stupid things again.
لا تفعل أشياء غبية مرة أخرى.
Even if I don't,
حتى لو لم أفعل ،
someone is still going to kidnap me
لا يزال شخص ما يخطفني
and kill me.
وتقتلني.
I promise you.
أعدك.
What happened yesterday
ماذا حدث البارحة
will never be repeated.
لن تتكرر أبدا.
What about that woman?
ماذا عن تلك المرأة؟
Is she
هل هي
really dead?
ميت حقا؟
That wicked woman
تلك المرأة الشريرة
deserved to die.
يستحق الموت.
What's wrong?
ما هو الخطأ؟
I'm just a little scared.
أنا خائف قليلاً.
By the way,
بالمناسبة،
why did you sneak off to Qingling Mountain yesterday
لماذا تسللت إلى جبل تشينغلينغ أمس
and deliberately leave Lu Jinyan behind?
وتعمد ترك "لو جينيان" خلفه؟
Well,
حسنًا،
I went on a date with Jingchuan.
ذهبت في موعد مع جينغتشوان.
He asked me out for a sleepover.
طلب مني الخروج للنوم.
How awkward it would be
كم سيكون محرجا
if Lu Jinyan was there.
لو كان لو جينيان هناك.
Is he the guy you worked with on the show?
هل هو الرجل الذي عملت معه في العرض؟
Do you have a crush on him?
هل لديك على سحق له؟
Can't I?
لا أستطيع؟
He is much more considerate than Lu Jinyan.
إنه أكثر مراعاة من لو جينيان.
By the way,
بالمناسبة،
I want to replace Lu Jinyan.
أريد استبدال لو جينيان.
Why did you change me suddenly?
لماذا غيرتني فجأة؟
The first basic principle of a bodyguard
أول مبدأ أساسي للحارس الشخصي
is to protect the safety of his client.
هو حماية سلامة موكله.
If you can't even do that,
إذا لم تستطع فعل ذلك ،
what qualifies you to be by my side?
ما الذي يؤهلك لتكون بجانبي؟
I know how hard it must be for you right now.
أعرف مدى صعوبة الأمر بالنسبة لك الآن.
Who do you think you are?
من تظن نفسك؟
Don't think you know me well.
لا تعتقد أنك تعرفني جيدًا.
Listen.
يستمع.
I'm fine now
أنا بخير الآن
and I know exactly
وأنا أعلم بالضبط
what I want to do.
ماذا اريد ان افعل.
What are you going to do?
ما كنت تنوي القيام به؟
I want to be Xu Xixi.
أريد أن أكون Xu Xixi.
So please don't get in my way.
لذا من فضلك لا تقف في طريقي.
Let Xixi learn self-defence from you?
دع Xixi يتعلم الدفاع عن النفس منك؟
Yes, sir.
نعم سيدي.
After yesterday's kidnapping,
بعد خطف الأمس ،
I think Ms. Xu
أعتقد السيدة شو
could learn some self-defence skills.
يمكن أن تتعلم بعض مهارات الدفاع عن النفس.
During my suspension,
أثناء تعليقي ،
I had nothing else to do but coordinate
لم يكن لدي شيء آخر أفعله سوى التنسيق
the return of the medical team.
عودة الفريق الطبي.
I can teach her.
يمكنني تعليمها.
All right.
حسنًا.
However,
لكن،
you mustn't forget about the medical team.
يجب ألا تنسى الفريق الطبي.
They will return in three days.
سيعودون في غضون ثلاثة أيام.
There is no room
لايوجد غرف شاغرة
for error in this matter.
عن الخطأ في هذا الأمر.
Yes, sir.
نعم سيدي.
Let go.
اتركه.
I don't want to learn self-defense.
لا أريد أن أتعلم الدفاع عن النفس.
This is Mr. Xu's order.
هذا أمر السيد شو.
Don't use him to pressure me.
لا تستخدمه للضغط علي.
I said no.
قلت لا.
The most effective self-defence technique
أكثر تقنيات الدفاع عن النفس فعالية
is to use the hardest part
هو استخدام الجزء الأصعب
to hit the vulnerable part of the body.
لضرب الجزء الضعيف من الجسم.
Temple, neck, chest.
المعبد والرقبة والصدر.
Let go.
اتركه.
I don't have time for this.
ليس لدي وقت لهذا.
Then try to break free from me.
ثم حاول التحرر مني.
Lu Jinyan.
لو جينيان.
Do you know why I don't want to learn?
هل تعلم لماذا لا أريد أن أتعلم؟
Because I don't even want to see you,
لأنني لا أريد حتى أن أراك ،
let alone be near you.
ناهيك عن أن تكون بالقرب منك.
Are you crazy?
هل أنت مجنون؟
It's full of surveillance.
إنها مليئة بالمراقبة.
This is the blind spot.
هذه هي النقطة العمياء.
Xu Yongyu won't see it.
لن يرى Xu Yongyu ذلك.
It's okay.
لا بأس.
If you're frustrated, let it out.
إذا كنت محبطًا ، فاترك الأمر.
I promise you'll be fine.
أعدك أنك ستكون بخير.
Do you think this is funny?
هل تظن ان هذا مضحك؟
Do you think I'm pretending to be strong
هل تعتقد أنني أتظاهر بأنني قوي
and need your comfort
وتحتاج راحتك
and venting?
والتنفيس؟
If you don't feel like it,
إذا كنت لا تشعر بالرغبة في ذلك ،
then try to push me away.
ثم حاول دفعني بعيدًا.
♪It's you who stay close to me to guard♪
♪ أنت من تبقى بالقرب مني للحراسة
♪In the name of love♪
♪ باسم الحب ♪
♪Without the need for extra consideration♪
♪ دون الحاجة إلى مزيد من الاهتمام ♪
♪Regardless of identity, memory or name♪
بغض النظر عن الهوية أو الذاكرة أو الاسم
♪I rush towards you♪
أهرع نحوك
Ineffective attacks are the last thing
الهجمات غير الفعالة هي آخر شيء
you want to do when you are outmatched.
تريد أن تفعل عندما تفوق عليك.
You can choose to use a weapon.
يمكنك اختيار استخدام سلاح.
Make sure you hit it right on the spot.
تأكد من ضربه على الفور.
♪It's you, my love living in my heart♪
♪ هذا أنت يا حبي الذي أعيش في قلبي ♪
Don't use your old tricks on me.
لا تستخدم حيلك القديمة علي.
♪I feel you more♪
♪ أشعر بك أكثر
♪I love you more♪
♪ أحبك أكثر
Tiancheng.
تيانتشينغ.
Did you find out the location of the phone number?
هل عرفت مكان رقم الهاتف؟
At the Xu family's house,
في منزل عائلة شو ،
heading for the gates.
يتجه نحو البوابات.
It is An Yue.
إنه An Yue.
No wonder.
لا عجب.
We didn't get a single photo yesterday.
لم نحصل على صورة واحدة أمس.
Please return the deposit.
يرجى إعادة الوديعة.
Just we didn't get a shot yesterday,
فقط لم نحصل على فرصة بالأمس ،
it doesn't mean we can't get one today.
هذا لا يعني أننا لا نستطيع الحصول على واحدة اليوم.
What do you mean?
ماذا تقصد؟
Look at this.
انظر إلى هذا.
(Newcomer, named Xu, has been kidnapped in Qingling Mountain.)
(تم اختطاف الوافد الجديد ، المسمى شو ، في جبل تشينغ لينغ).
Xu Xixi was kidnapped.
شو Xixi تم اختطافه.
As a boyfriend,
كصديق ،
shouldn't you be concerned?
الا يجب ان تكون قلقا
(Newcomer, named Xu, has been kidnapped in Qingling Mountain.)
(تم اختطاف الوافد الجديد ، المسمى شو ، في جبل تشينغ لينغ).
No,
لا،
we arranged to meet at Qing Ling Mountain.
رتبنا للقاء في جبل تشينغ لينغ.
Why did she go to Qingling Mountain?
لماذا ذهبت إلى جبل تشينغلينغ؟
Yes, I wonder about that too.
نعم ، أتساءل عن ذلك أيضًا.
I heard you on the phone yesterday
سمعتك على الهاتف البارحة
when you were planning your date.
عندما كنت تخطط لموعدك.
Unless...
إلا إذا...
Unless she was just toying with me,
إلا إذا كانت تتلاعب بي فقط ،
using me
يستخدمني
as a shield from the start.
كدرع من البداية.
Are you saying that
هل انت تقول هذا
she went to Qingling Mountain for another purpose?
ذهبت إلى جبل تشينغلينغ لغرض آخر؟
Perhaps she went to see
ربما ذهبت لترى
someone important to her.
شخص مهم لها.
Who?
من؟
Do you think I'm stupid?
هل تعتقد أنا غبي؟
How can I tell you
كيف استطيع اخبارك
something so important?
شيء مهم جدا؟
I'm going to use this
سأستخدم هذا
to get a good grip on Xu Xixi.
للحصول على قبضة جيدة على Xu Xixi.
(An unidentified woman's body)
(جسد مجهولة الهوية)
(was recovered from the waters off)
(تم استرداده من المياه قبالة)
(Qingling Bay early this morning.)
(خليج تشينغ لينغ في وقت مبكر من هذا الصباح.)
(The police are currently investigating)
(الشرطة تحقق حاليا)
(a suspected connection to a kidnapping.)
(يشتبه في ارتباطه بالاختطاف).
That report is false.
هذا التقرير كاذب.
Aunt An couldn't have kidnapped her own daughter.
لم تستطع العمة آن اختطاف ابنتها.
She couldn't have failed to recognise An Yue.
لا يمكن أن تكون قد فشلت في التعرف على An Yue.
She...
هي...
Sorry, I...
أسف أنا...
I don't know how to explain this to you.
لا أعرف كيف أشرح لك هذا.
You don't have to.
لا داعي لذلك.
I will cancel
سألغي
all her jobs.
كل وظائفها.
You two should have a good rest.
يجب أن تحصل على راحة جيدة.
About Mr. Xu...
حول السيد شو ...
I'll handle it.
أنا التعامل معها.
Close the door.
أغلق الباب.
Why did you call me here?
لماذا اتصلت بي هنا؟
It's okay.
لا بأس.
I am here.
أنا هنا.
I'm fine.
أنا بخير.
Let's go home
لنذهب إلى المنزل
and see Aunt An off for the last time.
وانظر Aunt An off للمرة الأخيرة.
I'm not going.
أنا لن أذهب.
Don't worry.
لا تقلق.
Tian Sui will deal
سوف يتعامل تيان سوي
with Xu Yongyu.
مع Xu Yongyu.
(You stood me up yesterday)
(لقد أوقفتني البارحة)
(to meet someone at Qingling Mountain, right?)
(لمقابلة شخص ما في جبل تشينغلينغ ، أليس كذلك؟)
I've got things to do.
لدي أشياء لأفعلها.
So I'll be off.
لذلك سأكون خارج.
What is it?
ما هذا؟
What is
ما هو
more important than your mother?
أهم من والدتك؟
There is.
هنالك.
To become Xu Xixi.
ليصبح Xu Xixi.
To become Xu Xixi?
ليصبح Xu Xixi؟
Yueyue, Aunt An brought you up by herself.
Yueyue ، لقد أحضرتك العمة An بنفسها.
Now she's dead,
الآن ماتت ،
you don't even go back to see her.
حتى أنك لا تعود لرؤيتها.
You only care about being Ms. Xu, don't you?
أنت فقط تهتم بكونك السيدة شو ، أليس كذلك؟
An Yue.
يوي.
Don't you feel sorry for her?
ألا تشعر بالأسف عليها؟
Everything I do now
كل ما أفعله الآن
is to be worthy of her.
هو أن تكون جديراً بها.
Ding Beifan.
دينغ بيفان.
Can't you see?
ألا تستطيع أن ترى؟
She is the one who suffers the most.
هي الأكثر معاناة.
Give her some space to be alone.
امنحها بعض المساحة لتكون بمفردها.
I'm just afraid
أنا خائفة فقط
she'll go off the rails.
سوف تخرج عن القضبان.
Where is An Yue?
أين هو An Yue؟
She just left.
غادرت للتو.
Didn't you run into her?
ألم تصادفها؟
Wait.
انتظر.
I think something is wrong with An Yue.
أعتقد أن هناك شيئًا ما خطأ في An Yue.
I don't know what she's been through,
لا أعرف ما الذي مرت به ،
but she
لكنها
doesn't look like herself anymore.
لا تشبه نفسها بعد الآن.
It was my fault.
كانت غلطتي.
Don't worry. I will bring her back.
لا تقلق.  سأعيدها.
I have something to tell you.
لدي شيء لأخبرك به.
Why are you standing still? Stop him.
لماذا لا تزال واقفا؟  أوقفوه.
Don't let him come near me
لا تدعه يقترب مني
without my permission.
دون إذن مني.
Yes.
نعم.
(Xixi.)
(يتبول.)
(I knew you'd be eager)
(كنت أعلم أنك ستكون حريصًا)
(to call me.)
(لكي تتصل بي.)
Jingchuan, I want to see you.
جينغتشوان ، أريد أن أراك.
I have something to say to you in person.
لدي ما أقوله لك شخصيًا.
Get out of the way.
ابتعد عن الطريق.
I'm sorry, Lu.
أنا آسف لو.
We are brothers.
نحن اخوة.
I don't want to fight with you.
لا اريد القتال معك.
We neither,
نحن لا،
but if you continue to follow Ms. Xu,
ولكن إذا واصلت متابعة السيدة شو ،
we'll have no choice but to take action.
ليس لدينا خيار سوى اتخاذ إجراء.
You had arranged to meet at Qingling Mountain,
كنت قد رتبت للقاء في جبل تشينغلينغ ،
but you were afraid those men
لكنك كنت تخشى هؤلاء الرجال
would find out and tell your father.
يكتشف ويخبر والدك.
So you used me as a cover for you.
لذلك استخدمتني كغطاء لك.
Qingling Mountain.
جبل تشينغ لينغ.
Xixi.
يتبول.
That was a good move,
كانت تلك خطوة جيدة ،
but I had to make two trips up and down the mountain
ولكن كان علي القيام برحلتين صعودًا وهبوطًا في الجبل
and my legs are still sore.
وساقي لا تزال مؤلمة.
When did you find out about it?
متى عرفت عنها؟
I knew it during the variety show.
عرفت ذلك خلال العرض المنوع.
He's been watching you, hasn't he?
كان يراقبك ، أليس كذلك؟
Who else knows about it?
من يعرف عنها ايضا؟
It depends on your sincerity.
هذا يعتمد على صدقك.
I was going to
كنت ذاهبا إلى
go straight to see Mr. Xu today,
اذهب مباشرة لرؤية السيد شو اليوم ،
but I'm too soft-hearted.
لكنني رقيق جدا.
I've heard a lot about
لقد سمعت الكثير عن
Mr. Xu's style of handling things.
أسلوب السيد شو في التعامل مع الأشياء.
I can't even imagine
لا أستطيع حتى أن أتخيل
what would happen if he found out
ماذا سيحدث إذا اكتشف ذلك
that his baby girl
أن طفلته
was dating a poor bodyguard
كانت تواعد حارسًا شخصيًا فقيرًا
and was kidnapped.
وخطفوا.
Yes, you are right.
نعم كلامك صحيح.
I did go to see Lu Jinyan that day,
ذهبت لرؤية لو جينيان في ذلك اليوم ،
but we weren't having a date,
لكن لم يكن لدينا موعد ،
we were breaking up.
كنا نفترق.
Breaking up?
انفصال؟
We broke up.
لقد انفصلنا.
Can't you see I've changed my bodyguard?
ألا ترى أنني غيرت حارسي الشخصي؟
Zhang Jingchuan.
تشانغ جينغتشوان.
I didn't know you had the guts
لم أكن أعرف أن لديك الشجاعة
to threaten me before.
لتهديدي من قبل.
If I send
إذا أرسلت
this recording of you threatening me to my dad,
هذا التسجيل لك وأنت تهددني لأبي ،
I don't know
لا أعرف
what he'll do.
ماذا سيفعل.
After all, my father
بعد كل شيء ، والدي
is not very good-tempered,
ليس مزاجًا جيدًا جدًا ،
especially when he knows someone is messing...
خاصة عندما يعلم أن شخصًا ما يعبث ...
Xixi.
يتبول.
I was just joking.
كنت أمزح وحسب.
Don't take it seriously, okay?
لا تأخذ الأمر على محمل الجد ، حسنًا؟
Then forget about the matter of Qingling Mountain.
ثم ننسى مسألة جبل تشينغ لينغ.
I'm sorry, Lu.
أنا آسف لو.
Well, Xixi,
حسنًا ، Xixi ،
if there's nothing else,
إذا لم يكن هناك شيء آخر ،
I'll be off.
سأكون خارج.
What's the hurry?
ما الداعي إلى العجلة؟
I need you to do me a favour.
أحتاج منك أن تقدم لي معروفًا.
At your service.
في خدمتكم.
Ms. Xu ordered us to stop you.
أمرتنا السيدة شو بإيقافك.
It's okay.
لا بأس.
Let's play by the rules.
هيا نلعب بالقواعد.
I hate guys who keep pestering me after a breakup.
أكره الرجال الذين يضايقونني باستمرار بعد الانفصال.
I want you to pretend to be my boyfriend
أريدك أن تتظاهر بأنك صديقي
and get rid of him.
والتخلص منه.
What?
ماذا؟
Are you not willing?
هل انت غير راغب؟
No.
لا.
That's not it, Xixi.
هذا ليس هو ، Xixi.
I'm afraid that he will...
أخشى أن ...
What are you afraid of?
من ماذا انت خائف؟
With me and my dad around,
معي وأبي في الجوار ،
Lu Jinyan won't dare to do anything to you.
لن يجرؤ لو جينيان على فعل أي شيء لك.
However, if you go public and say
ومع ذلك ، إذا ذهبت للجمهور وقلت
that I had an affair with him,
أن لي علاقة غرامية معه ،
I won't be able to protect you.
لن أكون قادرًا على حمايتك.
After all, you've seen
بعد كل شيء ، لقد رأيت
what he's capable of.
ما هو قادر عليه.
Give me five minutes.
أعطني خمس دقائق.
I need a chance to explain.
احتاج فرصة للشرح
I know what you want.
انا اعرف ماذا تريد.
I can help you.
أستطيع مساعدتك.
Are you helping me or using me?
هل تساعدني أم تستخدمني؟
Lu Jinyan.
لو جينيان.
I don't trust you
أنا لا أثق بك
and I don't need you.
ولست بحاجة اليك.
Then you can use me,
ثم يمكنك استخدامني ،
just like you used him.
تمامًا كما استخدمته.
Mr. Xu wants me to pick up the medical team
السيد شو يريد مني أن أقوم بإحضار الفريق الطبي
and they're going to give you a full body checkup.
وسيعطونك فحصًا كاملًا للجسم.
So I need to go back and arrange it right away.
لذلك أنا بحاجة إلى العودة وترتيب الأمر على الفور.
Clear Xixi's work schedule
مسح جدول عمل Xixi
for the next few days.
في الأيام القليلة القادمة.
I want her to take a couple of days off.
أريدها أن تأخذ إجازة لمدة يومين.
(Is Ms. Xu's body...)
(هل جسد السيدة شو ...)
Tian Sui.
تيان سوي.
Don't ask so many questions.
لا تسأل الكثير من الأسئلة.
Just do as I say.
فقط افعل ما اقول
I won't do the check-up.
لن أقوم بالفحص.
Don't fool around.
لا تخدع.
The result will be the same anyway.
ستكون النتيجة هي نفسها على أي حال.
I don't want to waste my time.
لا أريد أن أضيع وقتي.
Don't you care about me the most?
ألا تهتم بي أكثر؟
Do you want to see me
هل تريد رؤيتى
suffer again?
تعاني مرة أخرى؟
Xixi.
يتبول.
I can let you have your way with everything else,
يمكنني أن أجعلك تشق طريقك مع كل شيء آخر ،
but not with this.
لكن ليس مع هذا.
Dr. Zheng will be in Lancheng in three days.
سيكون الدكتور تشنغ في لانشينج في غضون ثلاثة أيام.
You must have a full medical check-up.
يجب أن يكون لديك فحص طبي كامل.
(Xu Xixi)
(Xu Xixi)
(Aren't you trying to let me use you?)
(ألا تحاول السماح لي باستخدامك؟)
(I'm giving you a chance now.)
(أنا أعطيك فرصة الآن.)
Dance with me.
ارقص معي.
Beware of surveillance.
احذر من المراقبة.
What do you need from me?
ماذا تريد مني؟
With Xu Yongyu's current stance,
مع الموقف الحالي لـ Xu Yongyu ،
the check-up in the next three days is inevitable.
الفحص في الأيام الثلاثة المقبلة أمر لا مفر منه.
Yes, Xu Xixi once resisted,
نعم ، قاوم Xu Xixi مرة واحدة ،
but Xu Yongyu never compromised.
لكن Xu Yongyu لم يتنازل أبدًا.
Since there's no other way,
نظرًا لعدم وجود طريقة أخرى ،
we now have only one option.
لدينا الآن خيار واحد فقط.
Find the real Xu Xixi
اعثر على Xu Xixi الحقيقي
to switch identities with her.
لتبديل الهويات معها.
Yes.
نعم.
Since my mother was prepared
منذ أن كانت والدتي مستعدة
to send me back,
لإعادتي ،
she must have left me a clue
لابد أنها تركت لي فكرة
as to where Xu Xixi was.
فيما يتعلق بمكان Xu Xixi.
I need to find her.
أحتاج أن أجدها.
Given Xu Xixi's temperament,
بالنظر إلى مزاج Xu Xixi ،
she will never cooperate.
انها لن تتعاون ابدا.
I'm not sure about that,
أنا لست متأكدا من هذا،
but this is the only way.
لكن هذا هو السبيل الوحيد.
Xu Yongyu won't let you out.
لن يسمح لك Xu Yongyu بالخروج.
That's why I need your help.
لهذا السبب أحتاج مساعدتك.
My help alone is not enough,
مساعدتي وحدها لا تكفي
you need Tian Sui.
تحتاج تيان سوي.
I will talk to Tian Sui.
سأتحدث مع تيان سوي.
You just need to show up at the restaurant
تحتاج فقط إلى الظهور في المطعم
at 8 a.m. tomorrow.
في الساعة 8 صباحًا غدًا.
Sir.
سيد.
Take a look at this email from Dr. Zheng's team.
ألق نظرة على هذا البريد الإلكتروني من فريق الدكتور زينج.
It's about Ms. Xu's check-up plan.
إنه يتعلق بخطة فحص السيدة Xu.
Tell them to get lost.
قل لهم أن يضلوا.
I don't want to have a check-up.
لا أريد إجراء فحص طبي.
This is
هذا هو
not negotiable.
غير قابلة للتفاوض.
Not negotiable?
غير قابلة للتفاوض؟
Xixi, what are you doing?
Xixi ، ماذا تفعل؟
Put down the knife.
ضع السكين جانباً.
You are always like this.
انت دائما هكذا
I have to obey you
لا بد لي من طاعتك
and do everything you say.
وافعل كل ما تقوله.
You don't even think about my feelings.
أنت لا تفكر حتى في مشاعري.
I hate you.
أكرهك.
I don't want to see you again!
لا اريد ان اراك مرة اخرى!
Okay.
تمام.
Okay, Xixi.
حسنًا ، Xixi.
If you hate me,
إذا كنت تكرهني،
I'll be gone.
أنا سأكون قد رحلت.
Just put down the knife.
فقط ضع السكين جانبا.
Put the knife down and I will leave, okay?
ضع السكين جانبا وسأغادر ، حسنا؟
Right away.
فورا.
So what if you leave?
إذن ماذا لو غادرت؟
This house is full of your informants and surveillance.
هذا المنزل مليء بالمخبرين والمراقبة.
This place is as annoying as you are.
هذا المكان مزعج مثلك.
I can't take it anymore.
أنا غير قادر على اتخاذ ذلك بعد الآن.
I've had enough of your control.
لقد كان لدي ما يكفي من سيطرتك.
- Ms. Xixi. - Xixi.
- السيدة Xixi. - Xixi.
Let me go.
دعني اذهب.
Sir, are you all right?
سيدي ، هل أنت بخير؟
Mr. Xu.
السيد شو.
Since Ms. Xu doesn't want to stay here,
بما أن السيدة شو لا تريد البقاء هنا ،
why don't you let her stay out for a few days?
لماذا لا تدعها تبقى في الخارج لبضعة أيام؟
I assure you.
أؤكد لك.
I'll make sure she's safe this time.
سأتأكد من أنها آمنة هذه المرة.
What is it?
ما هذا؟
Here's the thing, Mr. Xu.
هذا هو الشيء ، السيد شو.
A resort hotel
فندق منتجع
wants to hire Xixi as their Experience Officer.
يريد توظيف Xixi كمسؤول الخبرة.
Didn't you tell me yesterday
ألم تخبرني بالأمس
(that you wanted to give her a couple of days off?)
(هل أردت أن تمنحها يومين إجازة؟)
(I thought it would be a good opportunity)
(اعتقدت أنها ستكون فرصة جيدة)
(for her to stay out for a couple of days.)
(لها أن تبقى في الخارج لبضعة أيام).
I'm afraid she'll feel worse
أخشى أنها ستشعر بسوء
if she stays at home alone.
إذا بقيت في المنزل وحدها.
Okay,
تمام،
but on one condition.
لكن بشرط واحد.
Lu Jinyan has to be by her side.
يجب أن يكون لو جينيان إلى جانبها.
(No problem.)
(لا مشكلة.)
What are you looking at?
الى ماذا تنظرين؟
You didn't hurt yourself, did you?
أنت لم تؤذي نفسك ، أليس كذلك؟
Don't need to pretend at this moment.
لا داعي للتظاهر في هذه اللحظة.
To be clear,
لنكون واضحين ،
you and I are just cooperative partners.
أنت وأنا مجرد شركاء متعاونين.
I was stupid
كنت غبيا
to think you'd really help me before.
لأعتقد أنك ستساعدني حقًا من قبل.
Actually...
في الحقيقة...
I'm not interested in your plight.
أنا لست مهتمًا بمحنتك.
So you're not curious about
لذلك أنت لا تشعر بالفضول حيال ذلك
the phone call the other night?
المكالمة الهاتفية تلك الليلة؟
I met with your mother the night before
قابلت والدتك في الليلة السابقة
I left for Qingling Mountain.
غادرت إلى جبل تشينغلينغ.
I felt something wasn't quite right,
شعرت أن شيئًا ما لم يكن صحيحًا تمامًا ،
not at all expecting her
لا تتوقعها على الإطلاق
to be prepared to sacrifice herself.
لتكون على استعداد للتضحية بنفسها.
So she...
اذا هى...
She found out that Xu Yongyu suspected you
اكتشفت أن Xu Yongyu يشتبه فيك
and she was very worried about you
وكانت قلقة جدا عليك
and asked me to protect you.
وطلب مني حمايتك.
You...
أنت...
What are you to my father?
ماذا انت لوالدي
Are you guys planning something?
هل أنتم تخططون لشيء ما؟
Why do you want An Yue to pretend as Xu Xixi?
لماذا تريد أن يتظاهر An Yue بأنه Xu Xixi؟
All I can tell you
كل ما استطيع ان اقوله لك
is that your father and I
هل هذا هو والدك وأنا
have always been on the same front.
كانت دائما في نفس الجبهة.
We do everything we can
نحن نفعل كل ما في وسعنا
to keep An Yue
للحفاظ على An Yue
in good hands.
في أيد أمينة.
You really resemble your father
أنت تشبه والدك حقًا
when he was young.
عندما كان صغيرا.
No matter what happens,
بغض النظر عما يحدث،
you will protect An Yue,
سوف تحمي An Yue ،
right?
يمين؟
Thanks.
شكرًا.
My father and your mother
والدي ووالدتك
were in regular contact before the accident.
كانوا على اتصال منتظم قبل وقوع الحادث.
They must be
يجب أن يكونوا
very attached to each other.
مرتبطة جدا ببعضها البعض.
Yet they have done...
ومع ذلك فقد فعلوا ...
It shows that you are
يظهر أنك كذلك
important to them too.
مهم بالنسبة لهم أيضًا.
So
لذا
even for their sake,
حتى من أجلهم ،
for Tian Sui's
من أجل تيان سوي
or Ding Beifan's sake,
أو من أجل دينغ بيفان ،
you can't erase An Yue's existence.
لا يمكنك محو وجود An Yue.
They are all still expecting An Yue to return.
كلهم ما زالوا يتوقعون عودة An Yue.
How about you?
ماذا عنك؟
I am always here.
انا دائما هنا.
I've been waiting for you to use me.
كنت أنتظر أن تستخدمني.
I won't use you anymore.
لن أستخدمك بعد الآن.
That's okay.
حسنا.
It was my fault anyway.
كان خطأي على أي حال.
I shouldn't have lied to you.
لا يجب أن أكذب عليك.
Lu Jinyan.
لو جينيان.
I misunderstood you.
لقد أسأت فهمك.
I'm sorry.
أنا آسف.
I'm the one who should apologise.
أنا من يجب أن يعتذر.
I shouldn't have lied and used you.
ما كان يجب أن أكذب وأستخدمك.
I'm sorry.
أنا آسف.
I forgave you.
سامحتك.
What now?
ماذا الان؟
Do you remember what I told you
هل تتذكر ما قلته لك
about the three bodyguard principles?
حول مبادئ الحارس الشخصي الثلاثة؟
Bodyguards must protect their clients unconditionally.
يجب على الحراس الشخصيين حماية عملائهم دون قيد أو شرط.
Bodyguards must
يجب على الحراس الشخصيين
remain loyal to their clients.
يظلون مخلصين لعملائهم.
Bodyguards must not have personal feelings with their clients.
يجب ألا يكون للحراس الشخصيين مشاعر شخصية مع عملائهم.
And remember the fourth.
وتذكر الرابع.
♪My love in my dream♪
♪ حبي في حلمي ♪
♪Deeply hidden in my heart, no one can replace you♪
مختبئة بعمق في قلبي ، لا أحد يستطيع أن يحل محلك ♪
I will protect and be loyal to An Yue unconditionally.
سأحمي An Yue وأكون مخلصًا لها دون قيد أو شرط.
This one
هذا
takes precedence over all other principles.
لها الأسبقية على جميع المبادئ الأخرى.
♪I feel you more♪
♪ أشعر بك أكثر
♪I love you more♪
♪ أحبك أكثر
♪It's always been you♪
♪ لطالما كنت أنت
Then
ثم
what about the term of employment?
ماذا عن مدة العمل؟
Indefinite.
غير محدد.
♪It's you who stay close to me to guard♪
♪ أنت من تبقى بالقرب مني للحراسة
♪in the name of love♪
♪ باسم الحب ♪
♪Without the need for extra consideration♪
♪ دون الحاجة إلى مزيد من الاهتمام ♪
♪Regardless of identity, memory or name♪
بغض النظر عن الهوية أو الذاكرة أو الاسم
♪I rush towards you♪
أهرع نحوك
I'm sorry.
أنا آسف.
I just
أنا فقط
wanted to ask you what you would like to eat.
أردت أن أسألك عما تود أن تأكله.
This is not the time to eat.
هذا ليس وقت الأكل.
Let's get down to the real deal.
دعنا ننتقل إلى الصفقة الحقيقية.
Okay.
تمام.
(An Yemi, the project leader for the experiment)
(An Yemi ، قائد المشروع للتجربة)
Our priority now
أولويتنا الآن
is how to deal with Dr. Zheng's examination the day after tomorrow.
هو كيفية التعامل مع فحص الدكتور تشنغ بعد غد.
I once saw how meticulous he was about examination.
رأيت ذات مرة مدى دقة الفحص.
Basically, the chances of getting through are nil.
في الأساس ، فرص النجاح معدومة.
Our only way now
طريقنا الوحيد الآن
is to find Xu Xixi
هو العثور على Xu Xixi
before the examination.
قبل الفحص.
(Xu Xixi  An Yue  Twins)
(Xu Xixi An Yue التوائم)
But where is she?
لكن أين هي؟
My mother said she is free now.
قالت والدتي إنها حرة الآن.
So why doesn't she go home?
فلماذا لا تذهب إلى المنزل؟
Unless
إلا إذا
Xu Xixi is already dead.
Xu Xixi ميت بالفعل.
No way.
مستحيل.
My mom wouldn't do that.
أمي لا تفعل ذلك.
There is also a most unlikely possibility
هناك أيضًا احتمال بعيد الاحتمال
that the two of them
أن الاثنين منهم
were in cahoots.
كانوا متعاونين.
You're right.
أنت على حق.
If it was an inside job,
إذا كانت وظيفة داخلية ،
it would explain how your mother
من شأنه أن يشرح كيف والدتك
staged the accident in front of Lu Jinyan
نظموا الحادث أمام لو جينيان
and how she secretly switched two people in the sea.
وكيف حولت شخصين في البحر سرًا.
Driver He.
سائق هو.
(Xu Yongyu, Li Wanting, He)
(شو يونغ يو ، لي تريد ، هو)
I remember his words
أتذكر كلماته
after the accident.
بعد الحادث.
Lu.
لو.
It wasn't intentional, Lu.
لم يكن متعمدا ، لو.
Ms. Xu ordered me to speed up.
السيدة شو أمرتني بالإسراع.
I didn't notice there was a car.
لم ألاحظ وجود سيارة.
It just came out of nowhere.
لقد جاء للتو من العدم.
Lu.
لو.
I thought he was trying to shirk responsibility,
اعتقدت أنه كان يحاول التنصل من المسؤولية ،
but now it seems likely
ولكن الآن يبدو من المحتمل
that Xu Xixi made him speed up
أن Xu Xixi جعله يسرع
in order to crash into the sea.
لكي تصطدم بالبحر.
Even so,
بالرغم من ذلك،
we don't know where she is now.
لا نعرف أين هي الآن.
(An Yemi, the project leader for the experiment)
(An Yemi ، قائد المشروع للتجربة)
Remember.
يتذكر.
Under the juniper tree.
تحت شجرة العرعر.
I'll be waiting for you there.
سأكون في انتظارك هناك.
(The Tree Gin)
(الجن الشجرة)
The Tree Gin.
شجرة الجن.
My mother, she killed me.
أمي قتلتني.
Under the juniper tree.
تحت شجرة العرعر.
(An unidentified woman's body)
(جسد مجهولة الهوية)
(was recovered from the waters off)
(تم استرداده من المياه قبالة)
(Qingling Bay early this morning.)
(خليج تشينغ لينغ في وقت مبكر من هذا الصباح.)
(The police are currently investigating)
(الشرطة تحقق حاليا)
(a suspected connection to a kidnapping.)
(يشتبه في ارتباطه بالاختطاف).
(Did you send to the wrong person? Where did you go? I saw the news, what happened? Did you really die?)
(هل أرسلت إلى الشخص الخطأ؟ أين ذهبت؟ رأيت الأخبار ، ماذا حدث؟ هل مت حقًا؟)
(Take care of yourself. I'm sorry.)
(اعتني بنفسك. أنا آسف.)
(- The medicine has been given to you. - Why are there so many this time? )
(- تم إعطاؤك الدواء. - لماذا يوجد الكثير هذه المرة؟)
(- The village is safe. Don't forget to take your medicine. - You're being too verbose.)
(- القرية آمنة. لا تنس تناول دوائك. - أنت تطرف كثيرًا.)
(But I need to leave as soon as possible. Once I arrange it, this will be the route going home.)
(لكنني بحاجة إلى المغادرة في أسرع وقت ممكن. بمجرد أن أرتب الأمر ، سيكون هذا هو طريق العودة إلى المنزل).
(The chat record has been deleted.)
(تم حذف سجل الدردشة.)
♪I'm in the darkness all by myself♪
♪ أنا في الظلام بمفردي
♪Trying to look for you Wherever you are♪
♪ تحاول البحث عنك أينما كنت ♪
♪Did you know? I'm standing on this empty road, don’t know where to go♪
♪ هل تعلم؟  أنا أقف على هذا الطريق الخالي ، لا أعرف إلى أين أذهب
♪I'm calling your name♪
♪ انا ادعو اسمك ♪
♪If I had a chance to do this over again♪
♪ إذا سنحت لي الفرصة للقيام بذلك مرة أخرى
♪I know for sure it wouldn't be the same♪
♪ أعرف على وجه اليقين أنه لن يكون هو نفسه ♪
♪I can't stop loving you♪
♪ لا أستطيع التوقف عن حبك ♪
♪I can't stop love for you♪
♪ لا أستطيع التوقف عن الحب من أجلك ♪
♪My heart is saying it is very true♪
♪ قلبي يقول هذا صحيح جدا ♪
♪I can't stop loving you♪
♪ لا أستطيع التوقف عن حبك ♪
♪I can't stop love for you♪
♪ لا أستطيع التوقف عن الحب من أجلك ♪
♪Even though I know that you don't feel the same♪
♪ على الرغم من أنني أعلم أنك لا تشعر بنفس الشعور ♪
♪I can't stop loving you♪
♪ لا أستطيع التوقف عن حبك ♪
♪I can't stop love for you♪
♪ لا أستطيع التوقف عن الحب من أجلك ♪
♪My heart is saying it is very true♪
♪ قلبي يقول هذا صحيح جدا ♪
♪I can't stop loving you♪
♪ لا أستطيع التوقف عن حبك ♪
♪I can't stop love for you♪
♪ لا أستطيع التوقف عن الحب من أجلك ♪
♪Even though I know that you don't feel the same♪
♪ على الرغم من أنني أعلم أنك لا تشعر بنفس الشعور ♪
♪I'll let you go♪
♪ سأدعك تذهب ♪
♪I can't stop loving you♪
♪ لا أستطيع التوقف عن حبك ♪
♪I can't stop love for you♪
♪ لا أستطيع التوقف عن الحب من أجلك ♪
♪My heart is saying it is very true♪
♪ قلبي يقول هذا صحيح جدا ♪
♪I can't stop loving you♪
♪ لا أستطيع التوقف عن حبك ♪
♪I can't stop love for you♪
♪ لا أستطيع التوقف عن الحب من أجلك ♪
♪Even though I know that you don't feel the same♪
♪ على الرغم من أنني أعلم أنك لا تشعر بنفس الشعور ♪
♪I'll let you go♪
♪ سأدعك تذهب ♪